[
  {
    "question": "1. Who you are? (about your company)",
    "answer": "We are company who is specialised in providing solutions related to unsecured debts and finances, we have working in collaboration of six different companies in order to provide free finance assistance. \nNow continue with the reason I called you..."
  },
  {
    "question": "2. Where do you got my information that I got debt?",
    "answer": "So, basically we've got list of numbers of those individuals who are either making high payments or payments with high interest and charges, usually these details are transferred to us via different portals, such as CRF (that is Credit Resolution Forum), EXPERIAN, Credit Karma, and many more. Our job is to make you aware about the different debt solutions that will make it easier for you to clear you existence debts. \nNow continue with the solution that is all the high interest and charges..."
  },
  {
    "question": "3. How will you frezz down my interest and charges or How will you right-off my debts?",
    "answer": "So, basically there are 7 - 8 different options that are currently running in the Financial Market. So, based on you current situation and kind of debts that you are having, I will try my best to offer you the solution, that is as per your interest and not only this I'll also tell you all the benefit and the drawback of all the available solution that you are going to qualify for..."
  },
  {
    "question": "4. What are the names of solutions that you told me initially?",
    "answer": "Since there are options but you had insisted to know the name of the options, so it could be an IVA, it could be a DMP, it could be DRO, it could be Trust Deed, it could be Bankruptcies could be administration order, or it could be debt litigation. However initially I'm not sure about your current situation neither I'm sure about your current circumstance, so I want be able to give you the right answer, as to which solution is going to be more fruitful for you. \nContinue with solution and advice that you are going to get is totally free or cost..."
  },
  {
    "question": "5. Whats in it for you? or How you guys make money? or Whats the catch?",
    "answer": "We don't get anything from you as we get paid directly from the licence practiners once you case is approved and you are helply proceeding so oviusly the cummition is been paid but not by you. \nContinue with also there is no oblicattion for you to proceed with any solution..."
  },
  {
    "question": "6. Send me an email.",
    "answer": "Surely, we are going to share an email about the solution that you are going to qualify for but I'm prety unsure as of now which solution you are going to qualify for that we need some basic information about your debt whom you owe how much you owe and how much you making payments for. So that we can analyze your situation and can guide accordingly..."
  },
  {
    "question": "7. Is is going to hamper my credit rating?",
    "answer": "Since we are not offering any bankrupticy so it's not going to make you blacklisted and you can never opt any more credit, what we are offering is to have an arrangement so that moving forward you won't really have to comprimize with any expences you can have some saving for yourself, and if I ask you what are you current priorities, is your priority to clear these debts off, or are you looking for more credit and loans.\n\nCustomer: My priority is to clear my debts.\nSo, if your priority is to clear these debts off then you can clear these in a much more easiar and efficient way, becuase as of now since payment that you are making involves high interest and charges so what we'll do is frezzing down those interest..."
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is housing disrepair team?",
    "answer": "A Housing disrepair team is a group of people who works for an organisation that works for the tenants and they have certain damages on the rental property they are living in.\nWe make sure that anyone living in the UK is happy with the residential accommodation they have been provided by the council or housing authorities.\nIn case your complaint is not getting addressed then we will try to contact your landlord on your behalf because they can ignore you but they can't ignore us as we got a team of 10 different solicitors.\nIn case they have any property damage related issues unaddressed by their landlords as per the tenancy act {section 11} 1985 tenants you can also file a complaint against landlord, to resolve the problem quicker."
  },
  {
    "question": "From where did you got my contact information?",
    "answer": "We got your contact details through Housing Resolution Forum. It is an online web portal for the tenants who are residing in the UK on the properties provided by Council or Housing Association.\nIn case you have recently raised any complaints regarding the dissatisfaction in the living space against your landlord and it's been unaddressed by them, we follow up with those people who are in need of help to improve their standard of living.\nAnd also you don't really have to worry about anything because we are going to provide you legal protection as well because the major question that you might be coming in your mind could be: is it going to affect my tenancy agreement."
  },
  {
    "question": "How you gonna help me?",
    "answer": "Since, there are several options that are currently running in the financial market. \nSo, to tell you which option you will qualify and haw thử option is going to help you, we nud certain information from your side. Based on those inosmation I will check for the options will tell you all the benitits & drawbacks of the solution you can qualify for. So that you can make an infosmed decision. And the most important thing is — there is no fees involved."
  },
  {
    "question": "How you guys make money?",
    "answer": "It's the first time, I had got someone who has asked a financial advisor \"How they make money.\" But since you asked me, let me tell you,how i make - i make money through investments sometimes via referral fees where the cx, nuds any sort of insurance and switching off the gas & electric. So we get paid from those companies along with that we also get paid from license practitioners in case any reffered case had been approved."
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't know you?",
    "answer": "Neither I don't know you. It's not about knowing each other, its all about the solutions running in financial market and these information that I have got, I can assure you none of the person whom you know."
  },
  {
    "question": "I didn't asked you to call me?",
    "answer": "I know you never asked me to call and I didn't even have an appointment and I know that You are really very busy. But, let me tell you that what exactly is the purpose. So that you incase this is something which is relevant, you can ask for email or a callback also."
  },
  {
    "question": "I am busy right now (initially).",
    "answer": "Yeah thats fine, I can arrange a callback. But I don't wanna waste your time on this which is something irrelevant. So let me just tell you the purpose of my call."
  },
  {
    "question": "Never heard abord you guys, neitter the Debt solution, nor CRF?",
    "answer": "Well, no issues! I will tell you what is CRF and debt solution. Well CRF stands for credit Resolution Forum which is a government department who holds the \"information of the people who had some debt outstandings. OK? and they just passed your information to us, to let you know about some of the debt solutions which will help you to become a debt free person in much shorter span of time as if compared to the time taken by you, and if you are really struggling to pay your full payment back then, we will try to write off your major portion of your debts Alright?"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who gave u the authority to call me about my finances?",
    "answer": "Well, We have a Authority to help People with debts and finances in England, Wales, and Scotland. This authority is given once FCA regulated authorised company, so we regulated authorised companies are FCA we work under guidelines set up by the F.C. A Department and G.D.P.R."
  },
  {
    "question": "I have Never shared any of my details regarding my finances?",
    "answer": "I understand your concern but when you borrowed money from your lender at that time you might have signed Same terms and condition in the terms and conditions it is clearly mentioned your creditor they have the authority to share any of your details to any regulated department or company such as Debt Collector, StepChange, CAB, etc."
  },
  {
    "question": "You sound like a 'PAKI BASTARD'",
    "answer": "Well first of all sorry for my voice tone because I am new in this company and It is my first call so I am a little bit nervous and my manager he is standing just behind me - but don't worry I have all the qualification and knowledge to give you the right path for your debts and If needed I am also connect your call to my senior advisor they gonna help you in a much better way."
  },
  {
    "question": "Why are you calling me from a mobile?",
    "answer": "Well, As per the new FCA guidelines. All the FCA authorised companies have to use mobile numbers to call customers because from landline numbers so many scams had been recorded and because of this, investigation is going on every landlined number, and this mobile number is registered to our individual ID so if any report is going to be submitted against this number then the FCA team will catch us easily."
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't need any of your help?",
    "answer": "I understand your concern, might be our Services are not top priority for you at this point in time but we not only help you with debts, we have 4 to 5 different departments such as Eco4, Housing Despair, Loan Department, Charity Department so if you need help with other issues, we can proceed further."
  },
  {
    "question": "You tell me, how much debt I have?",
    "answer": "To be very honest with you due to compliance of G.D.P.R and F.C.A it doesn't show your exact information of how much you OWE and who you OWE, that is the only reason I am calling you today to analyse your situation and check what the best we can offer you."
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't want to share any of my details, you could be a scammer?",
    "answer": "Well, I am not going to ask you any of your bank details or soft codes of the card or any money so you don't have to worry about getting scammed. Our calls are recorded for training and monitoring purposes. So, we are here to let you know the best solution based on guidelines set up by the F.C.A department."
  },
  {
    "question": "How, you will gonna help me?",
    "answer": "Well, In these solutions first of all all your interest & charges are going to be Frozen down to zero Percent and If debt quality is successfully met then Some Portion from your debts will be written off as well. However, I can't commit anything ATM first of all I will review your case then I let you know which solution you qualify for and what benefit you are entitled to."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will, it affect my credit rating?",
    "answer": "I am not here to offer any bankruptcy or D.R.O kind of Solution where you will be blacklisted. In this, once you finish, you will have a fresh start in a new way, so you can get any loan, any credit, even a mortgage with low APR."
  },
  {
    "question": "How, you guys get paid?",
    "answer": "Yes, there are some commissions involved but it's not paid by you, it's paid by licensed practitioners once your case is approved and resolved happily."
  },
  {
    "question": "What, you need me to do?",
    "answer": "Okay, at the moment I am going to prepare a rough application notes to check which solution you qualify for and what amount of debts we can write off. So, if I talk about your total debt, how much you owe and then, start breaking down."
  },
  {
    "question": "I Know all the solutions, Why don't I go with the CAB rather than you guys?",
    "answer": "So you have the clear picture about all the options as you have experience this before and if you deal with the CAB or StepChange they are going to take a lot of time, couple of months to advise you because of their traffic. Basically, CAB will help you for budgeting and breathing space not for any options, and if you deal with them they will put your name in a government register then you won’t be entitled to get any benefits, and it will affect your tenancy agreement and credit score for a longer time."
  },
  {
    "question": "None of your business?",
    "answer": "Well, I am not peeking into your personal life; this is my job just to advise you and make you aware about certain solutions based on your current situation, so that you can save some money and have one less thing to worry about."
  },
  {
    "question": "None of your business?",
    "answer": "I know where are u coming from maybe my services are not the top priority to you right now. however, many of our clients found that addressing that help them I am just here to let you know some of the debt solutions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cold Weather",
    "answer": "Update on Cold Weather Payment in the UK: \nThe Cold Weather Payment is designed to support vulnerable individuals who are receiving certain benefits during particularly cold weather spells. \nKey Points to Note: \nThe payment is triggered automatically when the temperature drops to 0°C (32°F) or below for 7 consecutive days in your area. \nYou must be receiving specific benefits like Pension Credit, Universal Credit, Income Support, Income-based JSA, or Income-related ESA to qualify. \nEligible individuals will receive a £25 payment for each 7-day cold spell, which is usually paid directly into the same account where you receive your regular benefits. \nThe Cold Weather Payment scheme runs from November 1st to March 31st each year. \nYou don’t need to apply for it—the payment is triggered automatically when your area experiences cold weather. \nFor anyone concerned about the Cold Weather Payment, check whether you're eligible or see if payments have been triggered by visiting the UK government’s official website or contacting the relevant benefit provider. @all"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a customer is dealing with a private Debt Management Company?",
    "answer": "Well, if you're dealing with a private debt management company then I do believe that there's some management fees or set-up costs imposed on top of the payments you make towards your debts with them. \nAlso you would have to pay all your debts back with them or could be more than you actually owe as there's some fees included as well and there's no guaranteed freezing down your interests and charges on a DMP because it's an informal bond between you and your creditors and not a formal one. \nAlso there's an impact on your credit score too unlike the solution we're talking about which is a free of cost solution since it's the government backed up scheme we're talking about and it's something that is going to help you knock off a significant portion of your credit cards ,loans and so on to restore your credit rating to normal to remove all the black marks and all sorts of defaults from your credit file so that you could seek more credits with less interests and charges once you get debt free within a shortest span of time. \nYour interests and charges are also getting frozen down to 0% \nIt's something that is going to help you save some more money into your back pockets in these times of inflation which has gone up to 9.5% that is the most in the last 40 years which had made the utilities' prices go higher along with the fuel prices."
  },
  {
    "question": "For Falling Behind",
    "answer": "If you are falling behind on  your payments, i do believe your creditors might be chasing you by sending you letters or text messages  or emails to bother you. \nRight? \nDon't worry we will provide you legal protection against your creditors so that they dont bother you any further and  you know that your credit rating is being hampered badly so that i do belive you might face troubles in future in getting new credits for you. \nRight? \nAnd the program we are talking about will help you improve your credibility as well as it will help you to pay your payments more easily as all your debts will be consolidated as one and you have to make one single payement towards all your debts that too according to your reallistic affordibility. \nRight? \nAnd to give you a clear picture for which program you can qualify, what min payement plan is best suited for you, im gonna transfer this call to one of my senior supervisors. he will guide you further. please bear with me."
  },
  {
    "question": "If the customer is dealing with Step Change or Pay Plan?",
    "answer": "That's the reason you are getting this call where in we could check your qualification for a solution that might sound better than what have you got at the moment. \nIF YOU ARE dealing with step change obviously I do believe that they must have not given you any specific time period in which u will be completely debt free. HAVE THEY??? \nHowever I would like to tell u that the solution we are talking about is going to write off a majority part of your debts to get u debt free within a shortest span of time as compared to the time taken by them. On top of that  u have already gone for a kind of solution which has already had a negative impact on your credit score, therefore the solution  we are talking about here is going to help you remove all the black marks, all the defaults from your credit file so that you could seek more credits with less APRs(ANNUAL PERCENTAGE RATES) that too within a shortest span of time, once your debts are written off. Moreover, its a free of cost solution as well."
  },
  {
    "question": "High Payment (if he is making  300 or above)",
    "answer": "Right!! You are making such high payements.  Are you comprising with you these expenses or you are fine with these payments because as i can see  pound is such a high payement to make. \nRight? \nAnd also the majority portion of your payment are going towards your intrest and charges that's the reason your principle amount is coming down but coming down slowly. \nHave you ever noticed that? \nDon't worry sir we gonna drop down your high intrest and charges to completly 0% so that whatever amount you will be paying will directly deduct your principal amount and you will be completly debt free in shorter period of time. Also we will be looking for some possibility to write off some part of your debts too. \nTo give you a clearer picture for which program you can qualify, what minimum payment plan is best suited for you, M gonna transfer this call to one of my Senior Supervisor. He will guide you further...OKAY? \nPlease bear with me..."
  },
  {
    "question": "IVA Senario (Company name Debt Advice)",
    "answer": "The reason behind my call is that we received your credit profile today, which shows that you have got some unsecured debts which you are managing to payback. Right?\n\nWe're a registered Debt advice company and we've already provided debt advice to more than Hundred thousand people each year. We've been helping people to manage their debts.\n\nMenchester 2 circle square, Oxford road. Post code M17ED\n\nwe worked under the compliance of gdpr act & so we have limited access of your credit profile that's why I need to confirm from your End.\n\nWhat sort of debt you have?\nThere are more than 7-8 options running under UK financial market with different eligibility criteria:-\nWhat kind of debt you have?\nWhat level of debt?\nWhat kind of circumstances are you in?\n\nThen I will assist you with what are all the options which you can qualify for?\nUnited Kingdom is a free country for everyone to study and work.\n\nThat’s the reason I am calling you. We are promoting a government-backed-up program wherein all the high interest and charges will be frozen down to zero per cent. And if you qualify successfully then a major portion of your debts will be legally written off. Alright?\n\nGovernment is very keen to serve people those who are juggling with their finances.\n\nThe best part is that there is no fee involved. It’s a totally and absolutely free-of-cost solution for yourself. No monthly management fee, no setup charges nothing at all.\n\nHow did you get my number?\nWe got your information from CRF (Credit resolution forum). CRF is a forum which quotes the name and number of those people those who got any debt and paying high interest rates. So, we call the people to confirm about the current circumstances.\n\nHow did you know that I have debts?\nWe follow the guidelines of FCA and worked under the guidelines of GDPRS. So it doesn't allow us to see what sort of debts and how much is your total outstanding debts is? as these are the thing which we need to confirm it from your side.\n\nAre you compromising with your expenditure?\n\nSo now in order to see what best we can do for you I'm going to prepare a rough application note so you do mention that you've got a debt level round about ------------- So what kind of debts these are? Eg credit card or loans or bit of both\n\nOr you making payments with high interest rate and charges?\n\nAnd moreover, you do not have to make any decision over the call. This is a no-obligation call given to you.\n\nBreakage after getting initial debt level\n\nScenerio- 1\n\n10,000 - 400/m\nhow do you find these payments ?\n\nIs it ok for you or you have to compromising with any other expenditure to pay such payments\n\ncx no\n\nok that's really great that you are not compromising with your expenses, However the payments that you're making some parts of this payment are just going for the interest and charges and that's the only reason that your principal amount is coming down but a very slower rate have you ever notice that?\n\ncx yes\n\nSo what we are looking forward is to freeze those interest charges to a 0% so in that way what so ever amount u will pay it will directly go towards your principal amount and it will burn your principal amount in a much quicker time.\n\nAlso if you do qualify for a formal solution then there is a possibility that we can write off upto 50 to 60% of these debts and that too legally.\n\n ................................................................................................................\n\nhow do you find these payments ?\n\nIs it okay for you or you have to compromising with any other expenditure to pay such payments\n\ncx yes I'm struggling compromising with other expenditures\n\nDon't worry because our basic job is to drop down your monthly payments according to your realistic affordability so you don’t have to compromise with any other expenditure to pay such huge payments and you can save some money by end of every month\n...........................................................................................\nScenario 2\n\nare you paying by yourself or you are taking help with any other debt management company\n\n======================\n10,000 - 400/m\nhow do you find these payments?\nIs it ok for you or do you have to compromise with any other expenditure to pay such payments?\n\ncx no\n\nok that's really great that you are not compromising with your expenses however the payments you are making parts of this payment are just going for the interest and charges and that's the only reason that your principal amount is coming down but at a very slow rate have u ever notice that\n\ncx yes\n\nSo what we are looking forward is to freeze that interest to a 0% so in that way what so ever amount u pay it will directly go to your principal amount and it will burn your principal amount in a much quicker time\n\nAlso if you do qualify for a formal solution then there is a possibility that we can write off to 50 to 60% of these debts and that too legally\n................................................................................................................\nScenario 3\n\nare you paying by yourself or you are taking help from any debt management company\n\nDusra Scenerio-\n\nDebt level 5000/FB (Falling behind)\n\nSince when you've not making any payment?\n\nIs it a payment holiday that you've took from your creditors?\n\nIf No- So I do believe that you're getting chased by your creditors they might be calling you texting you or mailing you?\nIs any of these debts have been passed to any debt collectors?\n\nSo don't worry if you're getting chased by your creditors because onto the solutions that we are providing up in here it will provide a legal protection against on all of your creditors so by law none of your creditor will never be allowed to chase you or bother you in your personal life they can't send you letters or believe around and if by any chance they try to do so then we can also take legal action against them.\n\nAnd also since you're not making any payments so your credit rating is already hampered However on this solution once you come out of this programme you will get a fresh start on your credit rating all the black marks and defaults will be vanished. So in future you can apply for more credit and more loans with low APR(Annual percentage Rate)\n\nApart from mortgage and bills is there any other thing which you're making payment for like credit card bills, loans or unsecured debts.\n\nHave you ever missed any of your bills.\n\nThis programme is for those individuals who are not having enough savings and struggling to pay high payment bills.\n\nHow much amount you're paying for your bills?\n\nAns. eg 400\n\nWhat is the major expenditure that you pay on a monthly basis that you think is a really high payment for yourself?\n\nHow much amount you pay for your mortgage?\n\nHow much amount you're making payment for your debts?\nHow long do you have to pay these payments for?\nHow much is your total outstanding debts you've got?\nIs it roughly 5000-10,000 grand or more or less?\nHow much you're paying for that on monthly basis?\n\nTenant case-\n\nHow much you pay for your rent?\n\nAfter paying for your rent do you left with any savings for yourself?\n\nNo Obligation-\nJuggle-\n\nApart from mortgage is there any other payment that you pay like in terms of bank loans, credit card or debts?\n\nI'm gonna fill a rough application note on your name to see which solution best suited for yourself So before moving further, I just want to make you aware that this whole call is recorded under the compliance of GDPR and FCA for training and monitoring purposes. Is that okay for you?\n\nGP- General Physician\nCRF- Credit Resolution Forum\nGDPRA- General Data Protection and Regulation Act\nDRO- Debt Relief Order"
  },
  {
    "question": "Manage by himself",
    "answer": "JUST WANT TO LET YOU KNOW IF YOU PAY ALL YOUR DEBTS BY YOURSELF THEN AT THE END, YOU WILL BE ACTUALLY PAYING MORE THAN YOU OWE.. BECAUSE OF THE INTEREST AND CHARGES THAT ARE IMPOSED ON TOP OF THE PAYMENTS. HERE INTO THIS SOLUTION ALL YOUR HIGH INTEREST AND CHARGES WILL BE FROZEN DOWN TO 0% AND WE ARE ALSO LOOKING TO WRITE OFF MAJORITY PORTION OF YOUR DEBTS WHICH IS EVENTUALLY GONNA HELP U SAVE SOME MONEY AND MANAGE YOUR EXPENSES QUITE WELL IN THESE TIMES OF INFLATION. ok so to check which solution best suited for your self I just need to confirm how is the total outstanding debt you have"
  },
  {
    "question": "Minimum Payment (if he is making 200 or less)",
    "answer": "are you dealing with debt management company or managing by yourself? As i can see majority portion of your payment are going towards your interest and charges that's the reason your principal amount is coming down but coming down slowly. have you ever noticed that? don't worry sir we gonna drop down your high interest and charges to completely 0% so that whatever amount you will be paying will directly deduct your principal amount and you will be completely debt free in shorter period of time. also we will be looking for some possibility to write off some part of your debts. Alright! so to give you a clear picture for which program you can qualify and what min payment plan is best suited for you, i'm gonna transfer this call to one of my senior supervisors. They will guide you further. please bear with me"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why are you calling from a mobile number?",
    "answer": "1. I know discussing debt can be sensitive, so I'm reaching out directly. A quick phone call lets us connect personally and build trust, making you feel comfortable discussing your financial situation.\n2. We value your time, and mobile calls offer the flexibility to connect wherever you are—at home or on the go. Our team is ready to help immediately, answering your questions and clarifying your options in real-time.\n3. Your privacy is important to us, so you can speak freely in a discreet setting. Plus, mobile calls can be more affordable, especially if you have inclusive minutes."
  }
]
